{
    "subject": "resource/Wayland,_Kentucky",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Wayland, Kentucky",
    "human_readable": "The label of Wayland, Kentucky is Wayland, Kentucky.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9844205975532532,
            "question": "What is the label of Wayland, Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7966265082359314,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Wayland, Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6349616050720215,
            "question": "Where is Wayland located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5869733691215515,
            "question": "Is Wayland a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5565313100814819,
            "question": "What state is Wayland in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5385878086090088,
            "question": "Is Wayland a well-known place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4289087653160095,
            "question": "What is significant about Wayland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40412089228630066,
            "question": "What is the population of Wayland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3829391300678253,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Wayland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3286535441875458,
            "question": "Does Wayland have any other names?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Wayland, Kentucky is Wayland, Kentucky.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6539_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from Wayland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6539_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Wayland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6539_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is significant about Wayland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6539_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6539_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your question:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the label of Wayland, Kentucky is indeed \"Wayland, Kentucky\", as all the text snippets consistently refer to the city by this name."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that the label for Wayland, Kentucky is indeed \"Wayland, Kentucky\". All the documents consistently refer to a place called Wayland, which is located in Floyd County, Kentucky."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}